## PROJECT MANAGEMENT PLAN RESUME



## **CREATED BY:**

MUHAMMAD ALIFANANDA (1941720078)

#### PROGRAM STUDI MANAJEMEN INFORMATIKA

JURUSAN TEKNOLOGI INFORMASI

### POLITEKNIK NEGERI MALANG

2020

#### **SUMMARY**

Experienced PMP with a background in Information Technology with 2+ years Experience growing reveneue for Berkeley-based electronics firm. Seeking to leverage leadership expertise as project manager for London. IT Consultant in Grant Thorntn Internatinal in 2017. Marketing Managers at the Beckman Coulter Life Sciences for 2 Years Experience. Enterpreneur at SteamServe for 3+ years Experience. Chief Client Officer in Anser Advisory with 3 years experience.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **CHIEF CLIENT OFFICER**

January 2013- November 2016

## ANSER ADVISORY

- Managed the highly successful Lean Training project for 1 years, Improved quality by 42%, cut lead times 18%, cut cost 40%.
- Implementing capital acitivity in the public and private sector for over than 2 years in a wide range of senior.
- Specializes in working with clients t develop services and solutions that integrate service previously provided by multiplevendors to drive effeiciencies and desired outcomes.
- Serving alongside executive board members.
- Creating customer loyalty programs and offering customer success training for employees.

## IT CONSULTANT

February 2017 – June 2017

# GRANT THORNTON INTERNATIONAL

- Producing detailed reports on the efficacy of the technology.
- Analyzing a company's IT system and infrastructure.
- Implementing technological solutions to solve business problems.
- Provide strategic guidance to clients with regard to technology.

## MARKETING MANAGERS

November 2017 – August 2019

## BECKMAN COULTER LIFE SCIENCES

- · Optimizing marketing strategies.
- Managing the marketing department's budget and staff for 1 year.
- Promoting brand at trade shows and major industry-related events.
- Creating promotional information to drive business.
- Troubleshooting marketing campaigns that are not performing well.

# **ENTERPRENEUR**

#### STREAMSERVE

- Hiring talent
- Overcoming Bureaucracy
- · Obtaining financing
- · Develop business

#### **SKILLS**

- · Problem-Solving
- Leadership
- Organizational
- Time Management
- Computer
- Communication
- Project Management
- · Calmness under pressure

## **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science – Computer Sciences**

BERKELEY UNIVERSITY

## **Bachelor's Degree in Digital Business**

UNIVERSITY OF CAMBRIDGE

### AWARDS AND ACCOLADES

• Best Marketing Strategies at the Northeast Lean Conference in 2017.

# Organized

- Enterpreneur of the Year at IBA (International Business Awards) in 2017.
- Marketing Departement at IBA (International Business Awards) in 2019.
- Chief Client Officer of the Year At CCO (Chief Customer Officers) in 2015.

## **CERTIFICATE**

August 2018 - Enterpreneur University

March 2018 - Project Management Professional

March 2017 - IT Consutant Certification

February 2017 - Sales Management Certification

September 2015 - Decisioning Consultant

March 2015 - CAPM Project Management Institute

January 2013 – American Certification Institute

February 2009 - Product Management Certifying Board

### **LANGUAGE**

- English
- German
- Japanese
- Indonesian
- Spanish

# REFERENCE

- Best Project Manager Resume Examples 2021 [Template & Guide] (zety.com)
- Skills for a Resume Employers Will Actually Read (With Examples!) | Robert Half
- Licenses & Certifications on a Resume (Sample & Easy Tips) (zety.com)
- Ultracentrifuges from Beckman Coulter Beckman Coulter
- Best Project Manager Resume Examples 2021 [Template & Guide] (zety.com)
- How to List Certifications on a Resume (With Examples) (resumelab.com)
- Skills for a Resume Employers Will Actually Read (With Examples!) | Robert Half
- Who We Are Anser Advisory
- IT Consultant Job Description (betterteam.com)

- What does an IT-consultant actually do? Quora
  What does a marketing manager do? CareerExplorer
  What's it like being a marketing manager? | CareerBuilder